The clock on the wall is ticking slow. I'm
watching the rain fall. On the window I pick up
the phone, but I let it go. Just waiting for a
voice I know. It's just another night without
you. Another night I've got to get through The
city's sleeping but I'm awake Another night For
goodness sake
For goodness sake
The TV's on, but the sound is low I've got no other
place to go The silence is a heavy sound I wish
that you were here right now It's just another
night without you Another night I've gotta get
through Sitting, sleeping, but I'm awake
Another night goodness sake
for goodness sake
It's just another night without you Another
night I've gotta get through The city's
sleeping but I'm awake Another night For
goodness sake
For goodness sake
Goodness sake